Make America bait again!
Sharknado 5: Global Swarming is a action, comedy, horror
film directed by Anthony C. Ferrante.
Fin and his wife April travel around the world to save their
young son who's trapped inside a sharknado.
Fin Shepard, played by Ian Ziering.
April Wexler, played by Tara Reid.
Nova Clarke, played by Cassie Scerbo.
Gemini, played by Masiela Lusha.
Orion, played by Olivia Newton-John.
Electra, played by Chloe Lattanzi.
Sharknado 5: Global Swarming (stylized on-screen as 5harknado: Global Swarming) is a 2017 American made-for-television science fiction comedy disaster film and the
fifth installment in the Sharknado film series, following Sharknado, Sharknado 2: The Second One, Sharknado 3: Oh Hell No!, and Sharknado: The 4th Awakens.
The film was directed by Anthony C.
Ferrante, with Ian Ziering, Tara Reid and Cassie Scerbo reprising their roles from the previous installments,
along with newcomer Dolph Lundgren and the usual dozens of cameo roles by various celebrities.
In the film, lead characters Fin and April travel around the world instantaneously by going through portals
at the top of tornadoes in order to save their son Gil, who has been swept up in a sharknado.
They visit several places like Sydney, Rio de Janeiro, and Giza.
The sixth film, The Last Sharknado: It's About
Time, was released on August 19, 2018.
The film explores themes of cataclysm, tornado,
shark attack, time travel, sequel.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.